{
    "subject": "resource/Moloya_Goswami",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Dibrugarh",
    "human_readable": "Moloya Goswami was born in Dibrugarh.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8763858079910278,
            "question": "Where was Moloya Goswami born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8643109798431396,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Moloya Goswami and Dibrugarh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6743001341819763,
            "question": "Can you tell me the birthplace of Moloya Goswami?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6339483261108398,
            "question": "What city is associated with Moloya Goswami's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5302057862281799,
            "question": "What else is known about Moloya Goswami besides their birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5059416890144348,
            "question": "What can we infer about Moloya Goswami based on their birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4830528497695923,
            "question": "Are there any notable individuals from Dibrugarh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4684230387210846,
            "question": "In which Indian state is Dibrugarh located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42908063530921936,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Moloya Goswami's early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30024969577789307,
            "question": "Can you provide more details about the city of Dibrugarh?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Moloya Goswami was born in Dibrugarh.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8570_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Moloya Goswami's early life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8570_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which Indian state is Dibrugarh located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8570_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable individuals from Dibrugarh?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8570_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8570_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8570_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8570_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8570_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8570_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8570_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8570_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8570_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8570_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8570_60.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"Moloya Goswami was born in Dibrugarh to a Rajkhowa family\" which supports the statement that Moloya Goswami was born in Dibrugarh."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}